{
    "word parameters": {
        "excluded": [
            "abuse",
            "abused",
            "abusing",
            "assault",
            "assaulted",
            "assaulting",
            "rape",
            "raped",
            "raping",
            "molest",
            "molested",
            "molesting",
            "suicide",
            "suicidal",
            "kill",
            "killer",
            "killing",
            "update",
            "edit",
            "UPDATE:",
            "edit:"
        ],
        "minimum length question": "20",
        "maximum length question": "500",
        "minimum length answer": "20",
        "maximum length answer": "400"
    },
    "before": {
        "mean length of answer": "86.89312977099236",
        "mean length of question": "231.4618320610687",
        "std question": "181.08324514703017",
        "std_answer": "77.83994656372927",
        "longest answer": "804",
        "longest question": "1219",
        "shortest answer": "31",
        "shortest question": "10",
        "number of items": "262"
    },
    "after": {
        "mean length of answer": "85.29239766081871",
        "mean length of question": "189.7719298245614",
        "std question": "112.29498812620304",
        "std_answer": "64.45005229206608",
        "longest answer": "393",
        "longest question": "498",
        "shortest answer": "31",
        "shortest question": "20",
        "number of items": "171"
    }
}